I sell dreams and I built an ecosystem to make it happen, essentially.
What does that mean?
Let's get into it.
I flip houses, revenue is about four mil, just too much competition, I had a hard time
being profitable per flip, developed a model where we convert competition to collaboration,
vertically integrated HVAC company, roofing company, dumpster company, contracting the
whole nine yards.
And then started a coaching channel where I feed this ecosystem.
To be honest, I don't really care about the revenue growth factor, I care more about the
impact.
In fact, at least one million lives before I die.
So how do I do that?
I'm not going to be doing that flipping homes at a small scale.
But I built a company that's so based in locality that I'm just trapped within it.
What are you charging right now?
10k, nearly not enough.
Essentially training my own competition.
Hence why I did the whole vertical integration thing to maximize on that.
So much, you know what I mean?
Because you need to sell 400 people at 10k and you make $4 million and do none of this
shit.
Could you sell 20 people a week right now?
We will be soon.
You could have an 8x increase, so that would take you from 4 to 32.
And so you could probably realistically get to 100 million a year.
That solves the revenue problem, not the impact problem.
Do you make content?
I don't have time.
If you couldn't tell, yeah.
It would be far easier for you to just make content about the stuff you're doing, impact
millions of people that way, than try and get every single person in America to be a
home flipper.
And that's not achievable anyway.
I agree.
I don't know about the financial education, but you could be something more than just
where you think you are and where you came from.
And you can make content about that and you can distribute it for free with leverage.
It's a beautiful thing.
You can be legit because you have a legitimate business and then you can talk about it and
help all these other people.
And then you just keep growing this thing.